<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Academic Theme</title>
    <link>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Academic Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Your Name</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with the Academic theme for Hugo</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>The Academic theme enables you to easily create a personal academic website using the Hugo static site generator.
Key features:
 Designed for academic staff, students, or general personal use Includes Biography, Publications, Projects, News/Blog, Teaching, and Contact sections Write in Markdown for easy formatting and code highlighting, with LaTeX for mathematical expressions Academic linking (Scholar etc.), Google Analytics, and Disqus comments Responsive and mobile friendly Simple and refreshing one page design Easy to customize  Installation  Install Hugo and create a new website:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing content</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/managing-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/managing-content/</guid>
      <description>This is a brief guide to managing content with the Academic theme. Content can include homepage sections, publications, projects, and news/blog articles. After you have read this guide about creating and managing content, you may also be interested to learn about writing content with Markdown, LaTeX, and Shortcodes.
To enable LaTeX math rendering for a page, you should include math = true in the page&amp;rsquo;s +++ preamble, as demonstrated in the included example site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing content with Markdown, LaTeX, and Shortcodes</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/writing-markdown-latex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/writing-markdown-latex/</guid>
      <description>Content can be written using Markdown, LaTeX math, and Hugo Shortcodes. Additionally, HTML may be used for advanced formatting.
Sub-headings ## H2 ### H3 #### H4 ##### H5 ###### H6  Emphasis Italics with *asterisks* or _underscores_. Bold with **asterisks** or __underscores__. Combined emphasis with **asterisks and _underscores_**. Strikethrough with ~~two tildes~~.  Ordered lists 1. First item 2. Another item  Unordered lists * First item * Another item  Images Images may be added to a page by placing them in your static/img/ folder and referencing them using one of the following two notations:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>