<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academic on Academic Theme</title>
    <link>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/tags/academic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Academic on Academic Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Your Name</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/tags/academic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with the Academic theme for Hugo</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>The Academic theme enables you to easily create a personal academic website using the Hugo static site generator.
Key features:
 Designed for academic staff, students, or general personal use Includes Biography, Publications, Projects, News/Blog, Teaching, and Contact sections Write in Markdown for easy formatting and code highlighting, with LaTeX for mathematical expressions Academic linking (Scholar etc.), Google Analytics, and Disqus comments Responsive and mobile friendly Simple and refreshing one page design Easy to customize  Installation  Install Hugo and create a new website:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing content</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/managing-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-website-url.com/post/managing-content/</guid>
      <description>This is a brief guide to managing content with the Academic theme. Content can include homepage sections, publications, projects, and news/blog articles. After you have read this guide about creating and managing content, you may also be interested to learn about writing content with Markdown, LaTeX, and Shortcodes.
To enable LaTeX math rendering for a page, you should include math = true in the page&amp;rsquo;s +++ preamble, as demonstrated in the included example site.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>